dogshaming.com 2014-12-13

# Privacy Policy

At 0950702 BC Ltd. (the “Company”) we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products and services offered by us and through the Dog Shaming website (our “Services”).

### Information we collect and how we use it:

We offer a number of Services that may not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. However, in order to provide our full range of Services, we may collect the following types of information:

Information you provide – When you upload video, photograph or other content including written content onto our website, we ask you for personal information such as your first and last name, email address and other additional information (the “Personal Information”). All such information will be used only for the purposes for which it was provided, including, but not limited to, allowing the Company to contact you to get any further assurances required to ensure your compliance with the Terms of Use or obtain any further releases from you to make use of your uploaded content in any other media format and we agree not provide your Personal Information to any third parties for the purposes of solicitation.

Company’s cookies – When you use, visit or access [www.dogshaming.com](http://www.dogshaming.com/) or any of the Company’s other websites, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our website’s features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

Log information – When you use, visit or access [www.dogshaming.com](http://www.dogshaming.com/) or any of the Company’s other websites, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

Clear Gifs Information- When you use, visit or access [www.dogshaming.com](http://www.dogshaming.com/) or any of the Company’s other websites, we may employ “clear gifs” (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our Users anonymously (i.e., in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

User communications – When you send email or other communication to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

Links – We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising.

Other sites – This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by the Company. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

The Company processes Personal Information on our servers in the United States and. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

At a minimum, Company’s privacy policy must (a) notify users if online behavioral advertising (“OBA”) and/or multi-site data gathering (as defined by the DAA at [aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/)) is occurring; (b) notify users in plain English that information about the user’s internet use is being gathered through cookies, web beacons and similar means, and is being used to select advertisements so that they are more likely to be of interest to the user; (c) describe the types of data that are collected for OBA and/or multi-site purposes (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over); (d) explain how, and for what purpose, any data collected for OBA and/or multi-site purposes will be shared with and/or used by third parties; (e) contain a statement to the effect that third parties may also gather user data and that Company’s privacy policy may not describe the privacy practices of such third parties and (f) include a conspicuous mechanism by which users may opt out of such OBA. There must be a link to this privacy policy on each webpage where data gathering for OBA and/or multi-site purposes occurs.

### Choices for personal information

When you sign up for a service that requires registration or when you upload files, such as video, photos, or written content, onto our websites, we ask you to provide Personal Information. If we propose to use Personal Information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of Personal Information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use Personal Information for purposes other than those described in this Policy or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

You can decline to submit Personal Information to any of our services, in which case we may not be able to provide those services to you or allow you to upload content onto our websites.

### Information sharing

The Company only shares Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside of the Company in the following limited circumstances:

We have your consent.

We provide such information to our affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing Personal Information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to

(a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request,

(b) enforce the Company’s Terms of Use including investigation of potential violations thereof,

(c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or

(d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of the Company, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to Personal Information to the Company’s employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations subject to enforcement, if they fail to meet these obligations.

### Data integrity

The Company processes Personal Information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

### Accessing and updating personal information

When you use the Company’s services or website, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your Personal Information, either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

### Compliance

The Company regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or the Company’s treatment of Personal Information by contacting us through this website.
